
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following foods is a good source of vitamin C?",
    answer: "Oranges",
    options: [
      "Chicken",
      "Oranges",
      "Cheese",
      "White bread"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the recommended amount of physical activity for adults per week?",
    answer: "60 minutes",
    options: [
      "30 minutes",
      "60 minutes",
      "90 minutes",
      "120 minutes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following diseases is caused by a virus?",
    answer: "Influenza",
    options: [
      "Diabetes",
      "Cancer",
      "Tuberculosis",
      "Influenza"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a symptom of depression?",
    answer: "Insomnia",
    options: [
      "Insomnia",
      "Hyperactivity",
      "Increased appetite",
      "Excitability"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is a risk factor for heart disease?",
    answer: "Smoking",
    options: [
      "Eating a diet high in fruits and vegetables",
      "Exercising regularly",
      "Smoking",
      "Getting enough sleep"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the normal range for blood pressure in adults?",
    answer: "120/80 mmHg",
    options: [
      "100/60 mmHg",
      "120/80 mmHg",
      "140/90 mmHg",
      "160/100 mmHg"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following nutrients is essential for strong bones?",
    answer: "Vitamin D",
    options: [
      "Vitamin D",
      "Vitamin C",
      "Iron",
      "Vitamin B12"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is a good way to reduce stress?",
    answer: "Listening to music",
    options: [
      "Drinking alcohol",
      "Eating junk food",
      "Listening to music",
      "Watching TV"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a recommended way to prevent the spread of germs?",
    answer: "Covering your mouth with your hands when coughing or sneezing",
    options: [
      "Covering your mouth with your hands when coughing or sneezing",
      "Not washing your hands",
      "Touching your face frequently",
      "Sharing personal items like towels and toothbrushes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a complex carbohydrate?",
    answer: "Brown rice",
    options: [
      "White bread",
      "Sugar",
      "Brown rice",
      "Candy bar"
    ]
  },
];